Black culture is toxic.
And let's not, let's get on the fact that there's no fathers in the black house.
Let's get, let's get, let's talk about that.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
We all deserve a right to exist, and I shouldn't have to earn my right to exist, and that is
what capitalism does.
What makes you think that you have to earn it?
That's what I'm saying.
I don't feel that way.
You do have to earn it.
Yes, you do.
We are in America, Amanda.
That is why we are criminalizing the poor.
Well, here's what you all keep doing.
You keep interrupting me when I'm talking, and you don't want to hear the point that
I'm going to make, and yet you want me to respect your point.
And that's not how a debate works.
If I show you respect, give me the respect back.
Ooh, I knew I was going to be surrounded by ignorance, but damn, let's go.
My first claim is it is undeniable that reparations are just and necessary.
My next claim is that black-on-black crime is a result of underinvestment and over-policing.
My next claim is systemic racism isn't a theory.
It's our lived reality backed by data and history.
My final claim is black conservatism fails to meet the needs of the working class.
Greetings.
I am Amanda Seals, widely known as a comedian, an actress, a disruptor, an annoying person
on the internet who always tells the truth, and I am now an artistic intellectual who commits
myself to making art that educates.
And today, I am surrounded by 20 black conservatives.
Now, y'all know this is going to be a time.
So, join me at 7 p.m. Eastern on Sunday on my Patreon and watch with me this episode of
A Jubilees Surrounded.
One black radical versus 20 black conservatives.
See you there.
And next one.
Bye.